Finding Aid for the Music Center records LSC.3261
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 1: Music Center Operating Company files, 1949-2017
  - Dorothy Chandler's opening night Yves Saint Laurent outfit, 1964 (Box 727, Folder 1-2)
  - Dorothy Chandler's tunic, 1964-1969 (Box 728, Folder 1)
  - Hooded velvet cape, 1964-1969 (Box 729, Folder 1)
  - Usher uniforms, 1964-1969 (Box 730, Folder 1)
  - Usher uniforms, 1964-1969 (Box 731, Folder 1)
  - Usher uniforms, 1964-1969 (Box 732, Folder 1)
  - June Wayne Music Center artwork, undated (Box 733, Folder 1)
  - Jacques Lipchitz Peace On Earth lithograph, 1964 (Box 734, Folder 1)
  - Dorothy Buffum Chandler Man of the Year Award, 1964 (Box 735, Folder 1)
    This box contains a glass punch bowl from Beverly Hills B'nai B'rith.
- Series 2: Otto Rothschild files, 1930-2004
  Boxes 891-894 contain nitrate negatives which were deposited to UCLA's Film and Television Archive's nitrate vault on 2020 February 6.
  Otto Rothschild was a Los Angeles commercial photographer whose accounts included Kodak, U.S. Steel, Reynolds Aluminum, Carnation, Phillips, Standard Oil, Transamerica, and both the Republican and Democratic parties. Rothschild also served as the official house photographer for The Music Center, the Civic Light Opera, Hollywood Bowl, and the Los Angeles Philharmonic Orchestra. Rothschild held executive positions with the Los Angeles Press Photographers Association for decades and in 1969 he was honored with a life membership to the National Press Photographers Association, in recognition of his significant contributions to the cause of photography.
  Source: Top O' The Mall III, no. 9 (September 1970), Boxes 736-737, Music Center records (Collection 3261). UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
  The Otto Rothschild files range in date from 1930-2004 and contain biographical materials; Hollywood Bowl identification files; numeric negative identification files; alphanumeric negative identification files; 4x5" negatives; 4x5" nitrate negatives; 120mm negatives; 35mm negatives; 4x5" proof prints; contact sheets; 8x10 prints; oversize prints; slides; oversize slides; and a poster.
  - Otto Rothschild biographical materials, 1962-2004 (Box 736, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains biographical articles, House of Rothschild photographs, publications featuring Rothschild photography, project documentation, work orders, collection file, and deed of gift.
  - Otto Rothschild biographical materials, 1957-1987 (Box 737, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains clippings, photograph numbering and subject charts, California Living, and Music Center publications.
  - Hollywood Bowl identification file, 1938-1955 (Box 738, Folder 1-13)
    This box contains the following subjects: Artists, Ballet, Bowl Breakfasts, Bowl-Buildings and Grounds, Conductors, Crowds, Bowl Daytime Views, Easter Sunrise Service, Bowl Fountain Entrance, Historical, Operations, Bowl Night Views, and Orchestra On Stage. Each card in this box includes a proof print.
  - Hollywood Bowl identification file, 1930-1970 (Box 739, Folder 1-30)
    This box contains the following subjects: Orchestra on Stage, Opera, Off-Season Events, People, Personnel-Orchestra, Stage Construction, and Pilgrimage Play. Each card in this box includes a proof print. This box also contains an alphabetic subject index: Agnini to Nina Wulfe.
  - Music Center identification file, 1938-1974 (Box 740, Folder 1-6)
    This box contains index cards A-F: Claudio Abbado to A Funny Thing Happened on the Way to the Forum. The index cards include subject, date, place, event and photograph number.
  - Music Center identification file, 1938-1974 (Box 741, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains index cards G-M: Clark Gable to Odette Myrtil. The index cards include subject, date, place, event and photograph number.
  - Music Center identification file, 1938-1974 (Box 742, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains index cards N-Z: NAACP to Zorba.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1939-1948 (Box 743)
    This box contains index cards 1-104 to 5640. This box also contains a legend to the negative numbers assigned by Otto Rothschild, including subject, location, date and formats available: 4x5 safety, 4x5 nitrate, 35mm, 120mm, color slides, 8x10 or proof print, and prints held at Hollywood Bowl Museum.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1938-1946 (Box 744, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 5647 to 14137.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1946-1947 (Box 745, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 14138 to 22871.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1939-1947 (Box 746, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 22872 to 33502.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1938-1948 (Box 747, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 33503 to 43037.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1939-1950 (Box 748, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 43039 to 62809.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1950-1951 (Box 749, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 62810 to 73788.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1941-1952 (Box 750, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 73815 to 88331:6.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1941-1953 (Box 751, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 88332:1 to 100677.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1953-1954 (Box 752, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 100678 to 114215.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1954-1955 (Box 753, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 114216 to 127240.
  - Numeric negative identification file, 1955-1956 (Box 754, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 127241 to 137989. This box also contains the beginning of the alphanumeric negative identifiers assigned by Otto Rothschild: A3:1,2 to A3785.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1956-1957 (Box 755, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards A3787 to B6392.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1957-1958 (Box 756, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards B6396 to D280.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1958-1959 (Box 757, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards D281 to E3599.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1959-1960 (Box 758, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards E3600 to H3960:86.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1960-1961 (Box 759, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards H4010 to L5649.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1961-1962 (Box 760, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards L5650 to N5498.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1962-1963 (Box 761, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards N5503 to P6939.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1963-1964 (Box 762, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards P7007 to R6974.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1964 February 22-1964 November 9 (Box 763, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards R6990:1 to S5579.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1964-1965 (Box 764, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards S5580 to T1669.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1965 May 19-1965 December 22 (Box 765, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards T1670 to T7519.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1965-1966 (Box 766, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards T7528:1 to V1959:8.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1966-1967 (Box 767, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards V1990:1 to V4570:5.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1967-1968 (Box 768, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards V4602, Frames 1-16 to V8076.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1964-1969 (Box 769, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards 8168:1 to W379.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1964-1970 (Box 770, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards W380 to W2829:1-4.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1970-1971 (Box 771, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards W2830:1-4 to W4898.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1970-1971 (Box 772, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards W4919:1 to W6841:11.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1971-1972 (Box 773, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards W6842:1 to W8279:181.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1972-1973 (Box 774, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards W8281:1-4 to X103:434.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1973-1974 (Box 775, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards X104:1 to X1328:9-12.
  - alphanumeric negative identification file, 1973-1974 (Box 776, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards X1332:1 to X2258:5-8.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1974 May 20-1974 November 13 (Box 777, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards X2261:2 to X3195:9.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1974-1975 (Box 778, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards X3211:1-4 to X4190:259.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1942-1980 (Box 779, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards X4191:1 to Y18:41.
  - Alphanumeric negative identification file, 1942-1979 (Box 780, Folder 1)
    This box contains index cards N/N, and Y19:1 to Z14. This box also contains The Music Center Operating Company Archives - Otto Rothschild Collection stamp.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1940-1944, undated (Box 781, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 0000 to 1549.30.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1932-1942, undated (Box 782, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 1549.31 to 1730.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1940-1944, undated (Box 783, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 1731 to 4645.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 784, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 4651 to 5850.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 785, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 5856 to 7415.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1940-1944, undated (Box 786, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 7481 to 9030.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1940-1944, undated (Box 787, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 9031 to 11321A:7.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 788, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 11321A:9 to 13763.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 789, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 13764 to 16390.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 790, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 16391 to 18325:8.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 791, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 18422 to 20325.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 792, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 20326 to 218990.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1940-1944, undated (Box 793, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 21891 to 23690.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 794, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 23726 to 25930.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 795, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 25931 to 28165.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 796, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 28158 to 30868.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 797, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 31021 to 35335.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 798, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 35336 to 37500.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 799, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 37501 to 40600.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 800, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 40601 to 41925.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1940-1944, undated (Box 801, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 41926 to 44850.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 802, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 44851 to 50170.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 803, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 50171 to 52770.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 804, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 52771-55613.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 805, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 56554 to 62599.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 806, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 62619 to 65480.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 807, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 65508 to 66415.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 808, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 66456 to 67510.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 809, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 67511 to 70195.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 810, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 70196 to 75600.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 811, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 75601 to 77847:4.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 812, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 77856:1 to 81420.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 813, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 81790 to 84689.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 814, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 84727 to 87875.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 815, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 87876 to 82900:5.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 816, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 89201 to 92791.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 817, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 93228 to 96560.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 818, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 96561 to 98880.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 819, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 98881 to 100876.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 820, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 100993 to 103670.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 821, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 103751:1 to 109640.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 822, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 109641 to 112860.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 823, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 112861 to 113560.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 824, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 113561 to 116180.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 825, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 116181 to 119355.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 826, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 119499 to 122720.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 827, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 122721 to 124237.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 828, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 124371 to 127445.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 829, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 127446 to 130580.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 830, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 130581 to 137871.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 831, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives 135201 to A162.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 832, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives A163 to A3563.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 833, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives A3564 to A6739.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 834, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives A6740 to B178.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 835, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives B509 to B1869.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 836, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives B1870 to B3291.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 837, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives B3317 to B4950.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 838, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives B5027 to B6431.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 839, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives B6525 to C3262.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 840, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives C3308 to C6992.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 841, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives C7162 to C8916:3.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 842, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives C9014 to D89:1.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 843, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives D116 to D799.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 844, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives D800 to D3721:15.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 845, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives D3722:1 to D7378.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 846, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives D7540 to E1683.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 847, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives E1751 to E3674.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 848, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives E3746 to E4668.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 849, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives E470:1 to E9519.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 850, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives E9664 to H4180.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 851, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives H4217 to H6609.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 852, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives H6610 to H7991.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 853, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives H8004 to L1538.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 854, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives L1716 to L4159:4.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 855, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives L4451 to L6208.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 856, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives L6209:1 to L7926.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 857, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives L8003 to L9065.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 858, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives L9066 to N3277:2.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 859, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives N3327 to N6052.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 860, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives N6133 to N9479.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 861, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives N9504 to P1488.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 862, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives P1522 to P5616.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 863, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives P5651:1 to P9288.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 864, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives P9319 to R1119.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 865, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives R1120 to R2471:14.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 866, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives R2719:1 to R7433.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 867, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives R7436:1 to S887.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 868, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives S903 to S2032.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 869, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives S2066 to S3376.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 870, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives S3431 to S5584:16.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 871, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives S5587 to S7056.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 872, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives S7644:1 to S9647.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 873, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives S9721 to T1368.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 874, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives T1369 to T3160.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 875, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives T3161 to T4201.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 876, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives T4269:1 to T5484.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 877, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives T5504 to T6997.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 878, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives T7024 to T9981.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 879, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives V24:1 to V837:4.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 880, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives V840:1 to V1285:8.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 881, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives V1340:1 to V2478:7.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 882, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives V2510:1 toV4018:7.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 883, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives V4029:1 to V4994:8.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 884, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives V5000:1 to V7480:4.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 885, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives V7535:1 to V9979:6.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 886, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives W2:1 to W4827.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 887, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives W5029 to W9323:10.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1940-1944, undated (Box 888, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives W9486:1 to W9960C.
  - 4x5" negatives, undated (Box 889, Folder 1)
    This box contains negatives X80:1 to X4191:14.
  - 4x5" negatives, 1940-1944, undated (Box 890, Folder 1)
    This box contains unnumbered negatives which include LACLO.
  - 4x5" negatives, nitrate, undated (Box 891, Folder 1)
    This box contains nitrate negatives 1-125A to 122439.
  - 4x5" negatives, nitrate, undated (Box 892, Folder 1)
    This box contains nitrate negatives 122856 to R7434.
  - 4x5" negatives, nitrate, undated (Box 893, Folder 1)
    This box contains nitrate negatives 6918 to D1125.
  - 4x5" negatives, nitrate, undated (Box 894, Folder 1)
    This box contains nitrate negatives D3914 to R2505.
  - 120mm negatives, 1952-1967 (Box 895, Folder 1-8)
    This box contains negatives 89717 to V3971.
  - 120mm negatives, 1967-1969 (Box 896, Folder 1-8)
    This box contains negatives V3972 to V9991.
  - 120mm negatives, 1969-1970 (Box 897, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains negatives W8 to W3294.
  - 120mm negatives, 1970-1971 (Box 898, Folder 1-8)
    This box contains negatives W3315 to W6842.
  - 120mm negatives, 1972-1973 (Box 899, Folder 1-8)
    This box contains negatives W6887 to W9786.
  - 120mm negatives, 1973-1974 (Box 900, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains negatives W9827 to X3065.
  - 120mm negatives, 1974-1975 (Box 901, Folder 1-4)
    This box contains negatives X3121 to X4181.
  - 35mm negatives, 1953-1962 (Box 901, Folder 5-10)
    This box contains negatives unnumbered, 102500 to N9951.
  - 35mm negatives, 1962-1966 (Box 902, Folder 1-11)
    This box contains negatives P98 to T9898.
  - 35mm negatives, 1966-1970 (Box 903, Folder 1-10)
    This box contains negatives V17 to W2997.
  - 35mm negatives, 1941 May 22, 1970-1974 (Box 904, Folder 1-9)
    This box contains negatives W3021 to X2036.
  - 35mm negatives, 1943-1978 (Box 905, Folder 1-7)
    This box contains negatives X2037 to X4183. This box also contains oversize negatives, and negatives with proof sheets.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 906, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 1-125A to 5199.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 907, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 5206 to 12633.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 908, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 12806 to 21948.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 909, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 22112 to 33898.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 910, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 33939 to 45930.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 911, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 47603 to 65099:10.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 912, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 65203 to 69788.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 913, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 70075 to 84975.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 914, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 85147 to 95561.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 915, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 95896 to 107998.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 916, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 108043 to 118454.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 917, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 118500 to 130569.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 918, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints 130570 to A3699.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 919, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints A3700 to B5263.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 920, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints B5333 to C8875.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 921, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints C9014 to D7096.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 922, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints D7131 to H2292.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 923, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints H2293:1 to L5854.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 924, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints L5855 to N9479.
  - 4x5" proof prints, undated (Box 925, Folder 1)
    This box contains proof prints N9504 to R1189.